<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adolfo SBH</title>
    <link>http://adolfosbh.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Adolfo SBH</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://adolfosbh.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://adolfosbh.github.io/work/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adolfosbh.github.io/work/cv/</guid>
      <description>This site is not designed to expose a detailed Curriculum Vitae. Therefore you can access an on-line extended exposition of skills and experience in my linkedin account profile. Here, I provide a brief summary of studies and past work:
Area of Expertise
 Model-Driven Engineering. Eclipse-based and Java development.  Professional Experience
 Chief Technical Officer at Gaming Experience, mainly focused on managing the technical department that develops the on-line web platform and mobile app that provide services for gamers, 2017-2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://adolfosbh.github.io/work/eclipse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adolfosbh.github.io/work/eclipse/</guid>
      <description>The main expertise I&amp;rsquo;ve got during my professional career is focused on Java and Eclipse plugins development. As a result, I&amp;rsquo;ve done several contributions to different open source official Eclipse projects, and promoted as committer in few of them:
 Eclipse Orbit, main project where third party libraries are maintained as consumable bundles for Eclipse projects. Eclipse OCL, is an implementation of the Object Constraint Language (OCL) standard for EMF-based models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://adolfosbh.github.io/work/omg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adolfosbh.github.io/work/omg/</guid>
      <description>As you may find in their web site, &amp;ldquo;Object Management Group (OMG) is an international, open membership, not-for-profit technology standards consortium, founded in 1989. OMG standards are driven by vendors, end-users, academic institutions and government agencies. OMG Task Forces develop enterprise integration standards for a wide range of technologies and an even wider range of industries. OMG’s modeling standards, including the Unified Modeling Language® (UML®) and Model Driven Architecture® (MDA®)&amp;ldquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://adolfosbh.github.io/work/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://adolfosbh.github.io/work/publications/</guid>
      <description>During my doctorate and professional career, I&amp;rsquo;ve collaborated in several publications accepted in different national and international venues. A chronologically inverted list of recent publications I&amp;rsquo;ve (co-)authored follows:
2017  Adolfo Sánchez-Barbudo Herrera (supervised by Richard F. Paige and Edward D. Willink) Auto-tooling to bridge the concrete and abstract syntax of complex textual modeling languages, Thesis of my Engineering Doctorate Graduate, May 2017. PDF  2016  Achim D. Brucker, Jordi Cabot, Gwendal Daniel, Martin Gogolla, Adolfo Sánchez-Barbudo Herrera, Frank Hilken, Frédéric Tuong, Edward D.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>